gamingnewslink.com 2008-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Gaming News Link

Mar  
05

5 March 2008, Cake @ 6:33 pm

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [www.gamingnewslink.com](http://www.gamingnewslink.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

RSS Feeds  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our RSS Feeds (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site utilizes them. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Advertisers  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: god(at)mapuaownage.com

Related posts: 

  1. [Glinkster website facelift](http://www.gamingnewslink.com/2008/07/14/glinkster-website-facelift/ "Permanent Link: Glinkster website facelift") Whenever i publish a new article here in Gamingnewslink, I...
  2. [4chan’s Moot acquires 7chan](http://www.gamingnewslink.com/2007/12/10/4chans-moot-acquires-7chan/ "Permanent Link: 4chan’s Moot acquires 7chan") as quoted from moot on 7chan.org As you may have...

Gamingnewslink [](http://www.gamingnewslink.com/).

## Write a comment

Filed under: [Starcraft II](http://www.gamingnewslink.com/category/starcraft-ii/ "View all posts in Starcraft II") **|**
